murena.com Privacy Policy
-------------------------

As our project focuses on respecting user data, we know that privacy is extremely important to you. We do not share any individual information with anybody.

**About this Website**

The source code of the website can be found  
at [https://github.com/WordPress/WordPress](https://github.com/WordPress/WordPress). It is licensed under the GPL v2 license.

We use [Slimstat](https://www.wp-slimstat.com/) to create visitors statistics for our internal use. We use these statistics internally, for example, to measure how our website performs or which news site people come from. These statistics are not providing us any personal identifiable information. This information isn’t disclosed to third parties unless legally obliged to do so.

We use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You can do this through your browser (like Chrome, Safari or Firefox) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies settings. If you disable cookies, some minor features might be disabled.

We honour the do-not-track directive. If enabled,  
[https://murena.com](https://murena.com/) won’t create any statistics or cookie per your visit.

**Do we collect any personal information on [https://murena.com](https://murena.com/)?**

We collect information from you when you create an ecommerce account, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, subscribe to a premium storage plan, purchase a smartphone, or enter information on our site.

When you register to receive our newsletter by email, you will get news about new products and services. You may unsubscribe from any of these communications.

We implement a variety of security measures when you place an order and enter, submit, or access your information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

**What about the information I submit when I make a purchase?**

Those transactions are processed by third parties, and [https://murena.com](https://murena.com/) does not receive any financial information, which is transmitted from you to our third party vendors for processing. The name of the third party will be displayed at the time of the transaction.

We use Stripe, PayPal and Bitpay to process payments on this website.

**How do we protect personal data on our servers?**

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks at our partners and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

**hCaptcha and account creation**

We use the hCaptcha security service (hereinafter “hCaptcha”) on murena.io/signup. This service is provided by Intuition Machines, Inc., a Delaware US Corporation (“IMI”). hCaptcha is used to check whether user actions on our account creation service (and solely there) meet our security requirements. To do this, hCaptcha analyzes the behavior of the website visitor based on various characteristics. This analysis starts automatically as soon as the website visitor enters the account creation flow. For the analysis, hCaptcha evaluates various information (e.g. IP address, how long the visitor has been on the website or app, or mouse movements made by the user). The data collected during the analysis will be forwarded to IMI. hCaptcha analysis in the “invisible mode” may take place completely in the background. Website visitors are not advised that such an analysis is taking place if the user is not shown a challenge. Data processing is based on Art. 6(1)(b) of the GDPR: the processing of personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract to which the website visitor is party (for example, the website terms) or in order to take steps at the request of the website visitor prior to entering into a contract. Our account creation service needs to ensure that it is interacting with a human, not a bot, and that activities performed by the user are not related to fraud or abuse. In addition, processing may also be based on Art. 6(1)(f) of the GDPR: our online service has a legitimate interest in protecting the service from abusive automated crawling, spam, and other forms of abuse that can harm our service or other users of our service. IMI acts as a “data processor” acting on behalf of its customers as defined under the GDPR, and a “service provider” for the purposes of the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA). For more information about hCaptcha’s privacy policy and terms of use, please visit the following links: [https://www.hcaptcha.com/privacy](https://www.hcaptcha.com/privacy) and [https://www.hcaptcha.com/terms](https://www.hcaptcha.com/terms)

**How do we use data for Google account migration?**

During migration, Murena Workspace will access the content of the following apps to migrate it to the matching Murena Workspace app:

* Google Drive: all the files stored on your Google Drive will be imported into Murena Workspace’s Files
* Google Photos: all the pictures and videos stored in Google Photos will be imported into Murena Workspace’s Gallery
* Google Contacts: all the contacts saved in Google Contacts will be imported into Murena Workspace’s Contacts
* Google Calendar: all the events from all your calendars saved/accessed in Google Calendar will be imported into Murena Workspace’s Calendar.

We do not access nor store any other data related to your Google account but these elements. The content is imported into Murena Workspace at your explicit request while using the Google data migration tool available in Settings > Migration. The purpose of this tool is solely to make your migration from Google Workspace to Murena Workspace easier. Once the migration is over the rules described [here](https://doc.e.foundation/support-topics/services#can-the-ecloud-admin-access-my-data) will apply and the migrated content will be accessible, writable, removable at all times and only by yourself from your Murena Workspace account as part of data from this account. This means the data will be kept in your Murena Workspace until you delete it or you delete your account.

**More information**

For more information regarding the privacy policies of the following services:

* /e/OS and apps
* @e.email account
* the /e/OS developer portal located at [https://gitlab.e.foundation](https://gitlab.e.foundation/)
* the eFoundation community forum located at [https://community.e.foundation](https://community.e.foundation/)

please visit  

Murena Workspace’s policy
-------------------------

Our software does not send any of your user personal data to us.

We use [NextCloud](http://www.nextcloud.com/), [OnlyOffice](https://www.onlyoffice.com/), and [Postfix](http://www.postfix.org/) to provide our cloud services.

The following default apps mail/drive/gallery/calendar/files/tasks are linked to your e.email account and communicate seamlessly with your “own” /e/ server (through our partner Nextcloud). While these apps handle your personal mail, calendar and files, they do not send any personal data to us.

All data on your “own” /e/ server is encrypted and never shared, sold or traded to any third party. We will only disclose the limited user data we possess if legally obliged to do so.

Privacy Policy Changes
----------------------

We may change this privacy policy from time to time and we will update you when it is the case. We also encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes.

Contact
-------

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

MURENA RETAIL SAS

31 Avenue de Ségur

75007 Paris

France

Shop

Resources

About

Follow us

Copyright © 2024 Murena Retail

\-

\-

All rights reserved

**Select your country to shop online**
